I'm Peppa Pig. [snorts]
-This is my little brother, George.
-[George snorts]
-This is Mommy Pig.
-[Mommy Pig snorts]
And this is Daddy Pig.
-[Daddy Pig snorts]
-[all laugh]
Peppa Pig. [snorts]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[horn honks]
[narrator] Peppa and George
are having a sleepover
at Granny and Grandpa's house.
-Granny Pig!
-Gangy Ig!
Hello, my little ones.
Bye-bye. See you later.
-Bye-bye, Mommy.
-[George snorts]
[horn honks]
Come and see where you're going
to sleep tonight.
[Peppa & George giggling]
This was Mommy Pig's room
when she was little.
In olden times.
And this is the bed Mommy slept on.
Ooh, bouncy bed.
[Peppa & George giggling]
You're like your mommy
when she was little.
-[snorts] Did Mommy bounce on the bed?
-Of course.
But Mommy tells us
not to bounce on the beds.
[snorts] When Mommy was little,
she was cheeky like you.
Was she?
-[chuckles] Yes.
[both giggle]
Now, let's go and see Grandpa Pig
in the garden.
[Peppa & George giggling]
-Grandpa Pig!
-Baba Ig.
[snorts] Hello, Peppa. Hello, George.
Come and see my carrots.
[narrator] Grandpa Pig is very proud
of his vegetables.
[Peppa & George] Ooh.
And here are my peas.
[Peppa & George] Ahh.
But best of all are my lettuces.
Oh, no!
My lettuces!
I think the birds have eaten them,
Grandpa.
Yes. Birds.
Why didn't Mr. Scarecrow scare them away?
Because the birds that ate my lettuces
are very stupid. [snorts]
What's the matter?
Your friends have been eating
my vegetables again.
-Which friends?
-Tom, Dick and Harry.
[chickens clucking]
Those aren't their names.
[narrator] Granny Pig has chickens.
Wow!
Say hello to Jemima, Sarah and Vanessa.
-Hello.
-[George snorts]
And here is Neville.
[crows]
Is Neville a boy chicken?
Yes, Peppa, he's a cockerel.
[snorts] He's the worst.
Scratching up my vegetables.
[Granny Pig] Neville wouldn't hurt a fly.
[Grandpa Pig] I've seen him eat flies.
[Peppa & George] Ew!
And he ate my lettuce.
You don't want to eat Grandpa's lettuce,
do you?
[chickens clucking]
Not when there's lovely corn to eat.
Come on. This way home.
Peppa, George, would you like
to feed corn to the chickens?
Yes, please, Granny.
[George snorts]
Here you are, chickens. [snorts] Eat up.
Ooh, you've got a Wendy house.
That's the chicken coop.
It's where the chickens lay their eggs.
Eggs? I can't see any eggs.
Not now, but there will be eggs soon.
[Peppa & George] Ooh.
[narrator] It is bedtime for Peppa
and George
at Granny and Grandpa's house.
[both giggling]
Have the chickens laid their eggs yet,
Granny?
-Maybe in the morning, Peppa.
-How will we know when it's morning?
Neville will tell us.
Now, go to sleep.
[Peppa & George] Night, night.
[Peppa & George snoring]
[narrator] It is morning.
[both snoring]
[Neville crows]
It's Neville!
[Peppa & George giggling]
[snorts] Thank you
for waking us up, Neville.
[crows]
[giggles] Cock-a-doodle-doo! [laughs]
Good morning, Jemima, Sarah and Vanessa.
-Do you have any eggs for us?
-One, two, three, four.
Four eggs, Granny.
Now we'll have eggs for breakfast.
Thank you, Jemima, Sarah and Vanessa.
-[chickens clucking]
-[Peppa & George giggling]
Boiled eggs for everyone.
[Peppa & George] Hooray!
-Mm. Delicious.
-[snorts]
Granny, your chickens make yummy eggs.
Yes. It's all that lovely corn they eat.
And my lettuces.
[all laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It's the end of another day
at Peppa's playgroup.
Children, tomorrow is Talent Day.
[snorts] What is a talent?
A talent is something you like doing
and you're good at.
[bleats] I like to watch television
and I'm good at it.
Think of something
we might like to see you do.
My talent is playing the guitar.
[playing rock riff]
[all] Ooh.
[parents chatter]
[narrator] The parents have arrived
to pick up the children.
Don't forget to think of something to do
for Talent Day tomorrow.
[plays rock riff]
[narrator] It is bedtime for Peppa
and George.
I can't go to bed yet.
[snorts] I haven't got a talent
to show tomorrow.
But you have lots of talents, Peppa.
Yes. I can skip.
I can sing.
♪ Twinkle, twinkle, little star ♪
I can dance.
[upbeat rock music playing on stereo]
It's hard to choose one talent.
I am good at lots of things.
Don't worry.
-You can decide tomorrow.
-Okay.
[bell rings]
[narrator] It is Talent Day.
My talents are skipping,
singing and dancing.
I practiced them all last night.
I was practicing watching television
last night.
[snorts] That's not a talent.
Madame Gazelle said so.
What can I do, then?
Who would like to show us
their talent first?
[Danny woofs]
Danny Dog?
I can bang a drum.
I can bang it louder.
No. That was lovely, Danny.
-[Pedro neighs]
-Pedro Pony, what is your talent?
Magic tricks. [clears throat]
Here is a glass of water.
It is wet and see-through.
[students] Ahh.
Now I will make the water disappear.
[students] Ooh.
Please close your eyes.
Open your eyes.
[students gasp]
[narrator] The water has gone.
Thank you.
[Emily trumpets]
Emily Elephant.
I'm going to play the recorder.
[playing "Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star"]
-[Rebecca squeaks]
-And what is your talent, Rebecca?
I can make a special noise.
[trills]
It only works if I go up on my tiptoes.
[trilling]
That was very good.
Yes, but what can I do?
Candy, what is your talent?
Skipping.
I was going to do skipping.
But I can still do dancing and singing.
My talent is singing.
♪ Twinkle, twinkle, little star ♪
I can still do dancing.
[Madame Gazelle] Suzy Sheep,
what is your talent?
Dancing.
No, you can't dance.
[narrator] Oh, dear.
Dancing was Peppa's last talent.
[band playing
"Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star"]
It is so nice that everyone has chosen
a different talent to perform.
Now, who do we have left? Peppa.
I was going to skip or sing or dance,
but they've all been done.
A talent can be anything, Peppa.
But not watching television.
Think of something you really like to do.
[snorts] I know.
I've got a talent that I'm really good at.
[narrator] I wonder
what Peppa's talent can be.
My special talent that I am the best at
in the whole world
is jumping up and down
in muddy puddles! [giggling]
[narrator] Peppa loves jumping up and down
in muddy puddles.
Everyone loves jumping up and down
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is a lovely sunny day.
Peppa is playing with her bouncy ball.
George and his friend Edmond Elephant
are playing with their space toys.
[George & Edmond giggle]
Moon! Moon!
[narrator] George is pretending
that the bouncy ball is the moon.
[snorts] I was playing with that ball.
Oh!
[narrator] Edmond's space toy has landed
on Peppa's head.
-[George & Edmond laugh]
-[laughs] This looks fun.
Are you going to the moon?
[George snorts]
It's just boring space stuff for babies,
Daddy. It's not real.
But space is real, Peppa,
and there are real rockets
that go to the moon.
The museum has a show all about the moon.
-Should we go and see it?
-[George & Edmond] Yay!
Will we really have to go to the moon?
No, Peppa. We're not going to the moon.
We're going to the museum.
Okay.
[narrator] Here is the museum.
[all laugh]
Hello, everyone.
Have you come to see the moon show?
[snorts] Yes, Miss Rabbit.
Five tickets, please.
There you are.
Enjoy your trip to the moon.
Oh, we really are going to the moon.
No, Peppa. It's just pretend.
This way for A Trip to the Moon.
[narrator] Mr. Rabbit is the tour guide.
[children] Ooh.
Prepare for takeoff.
[snorts] It's just pretend, isn't it?
That's right, Peppa. It's just pretend.
[man on recording]
Five, four, three, two, one.
Blastoff.
We live on a planet.
-Does anyone know what it is called?
-The Earth.
That's right.
Oh-ho. I'm a bit of an expert
at space things.
There are seven other planets
that go around our sun.
Does anyone know what they are called?
Uh...
-Mercury.
-Ooh. Well done, Edmond.
Venus, Mars, Jupiter, Saturn,
Neptune, Uranus.
[narrator] Edmond knows all about space.
I'm a clever clogs.
[Edmond trumpets]
[all laugh]
Does anyone know what these planets
are made off?
They're made of cardboard.
[Mr. Rabbit] These models are made
of cardboard,
but the real planets are made of rock
and ice and gas.
But of course, the moon is made of cheese.
[all laugh]
No, the moon is made of rock,
and this is a serious tour.
So, no jokes and no giggling.
Here we are, on the moon.
It's a pretend moon really, isn't it?
Yes. If this was the real moon,
you could jump over my head.
Ooh.
Does anyone know
why we can jump so high on the moon?
Gravity.
Oh, that's right, Edmond.
Gravity is what keeps us on the ground.
It is weaker on the moon,
so, you can jump higher.
[Edmond & pigs] Ooh.
We can make you feel like you're jumping
on the moon with the help of science.
That sounds impressive.
How do you do that?
With big rubber bands.
[narrator] Everyone's strapped into
Mr. Rabbit's Antigravity Rubber Bands.
[all laughing]
[narrator] Bouncing on the pretend moon
is fun.
Say "Moon cheese."
[all] Moon Cheese.
And that is the end of the tour.
Please walk this way.
-Are there trees on the moon?
-No.
Are there any cars on the moon?
No.
Are there any moon shops?
No, that would be silly.
Welcome to the moon shop.
We've got moon maps, moon books,
even a picture of piggies on the moon
with an elephant.
[snorts] Look, there we are
jumping on the moon.
We've got moon rock, too.
It's got a picture of the moon
through the middle.
[Peppa] Ooh.
How about some real moon cheese?
How much is it, Miss Rabbit?
Five pounds, please.
Five pounds?
It's all for a good cause.
I like the moon now
because it's very interesting.
Mm.
And very tasty.
[all laughing]
[children giggling]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Grandpa Pig
is looking after Peppa and George.
Now, Grandpa,
I will tell you how everything works.
-[snorts] This is the slide.
-Whee!
You climb up here
and you slide down there.
Whee!
[Peppa] And everyone takes it in turns.
-[Grandpa Pig snorts] Ho-ho!
-Whee!
I know what a slide is, Peppa.
I used to play on one myself
when I was a little piggy.
Did you have swings, too,
in the olden days?
Ho-ho! We had swings and climbing frames
and roundabouts.
-Oh!
-But my favorite was the slide.
It is my favorite, too.
[Peppa giggles, then snorts] Whee!
[narrator] Everyone takes it in turns
to have a go on the slide.
Whee! [giggles]
Naughty Richard.
You know you have to wait your turn.
[narrator] Richard Rabbit finds it hard
to wait his turn.
[Richard crying]
Oh, dear.
It's not easy being small, is it, Richard?
[Richard sobs]
[snorts] Because Richard is little,
I don't think he should have to wait.
I wouldn't change the rules if I were you,
Grandpa Pig.
Nonsense.
The children understand, don't you?
[Richard giggling]
Whee!
But, Grandpa, George is little
and he has to wait his turn.
[George crying]
Yes, George is little.
So, he shouldn't have to wait either.
[George giggles] Whee!
[Richard giggles]
[narrator] Oh, dear. Richard and George
are taking all the turns on the slide.
Grandpa,
when do we get to go on the slide?
Don't worry, Peppa.
They won't be on it for long.
[sighs] I'm bored of waiting.
Me, too. Let's play on the swing.
[children giggling]
[narrator] Here is Pedro Pony
on the swing.
[Pedro neighs]
[snorts] Pedro, can I have a go now?
I just want to swing a bit more.
But you've been on the swing for ages.
Grandpa Pig, can you push me a little bit,
please?
I think it is someone else's turn now,
Pedro.
But I have to go home soon.
Oh, I see. That's different.
Let me push you, then.
But, Grandpa.
[Pedro giggling]
I'm bored of waiting.
-Me, too.
-And me.
[woofs] Let's play on the roundabout.
[narrator] Everyone wants to get
on the roundabout.
Too many children on the roundabout.
Everybody off.
[children sigh]
But, Grandpa Pig,
I was actually here first.
Ah. Then you can get back
on the roundabout.
I need to get on, too.
Oh, why's that, Rebecca?
Um... because it's my birthday soon.
-Oh. Oh, okay.
-[Rebecca giggles]
-[girls] And me.
-All right.
[girls giggle]
Is everybody ready?
[girls] Yes.
[woofs] Stop.
There are no boys on the roundabout.
-Um...
-[Danny giggles]
Now is everybody ready?
I'm wearing glasses.
Can I go on, please?
[narrator] The children are making up
their own rules.
I need to get on
because I like carrots. [giggles]
Now are you all ready to go?
No. I have to get on
because I can do this:
[blows raspberry]
[children giggling]
[narrator] Here is Mommy Pig.
[snorts] How are you getting on,
Grandpa Pig?
I'm confused.
These playground rules
are too complicated.
There is only one rule, Grandpa Pig,
and that is everyone waits their turn.
Whee! [giggles]
What? Even the little ones?
[Mommy Pig] Even the little ones.
What about the very old ones like Grandpa?
Even the very old ones like Grandpa.
[narrator] At the playground,
everyone has their turn.
Whee!
[all laughing]
-[child giggles]
-[Peppa snorts]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
-[child giggles]
[Peppa snorts]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
-[Peppa snorts]
-[children giggle]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
-[Peppa snorts]
-[children giggle]